Marketplace[](#)

1. [Home](https://classifieds.arkansasonline.com/marketplace-littlerock/)

Keyword

OK

1. [Home](https://classifieds.arkansasonline.com/marketplace-littlerock/)

Terms & Conditions

Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy
==============================================

We previously had 2 sign-in areas available on our homepage at starclassifieds.com: One for our listings site (starclassifieds.com) for users to save ads as favourites, and another for our customers to book/update their ad orders. The 2 sign-in's were causing confusion with many users, so we decided to remove the sign-in for our listings site. The only sign-in available now is for users/customers to place or edit their orders.

Please read these terms of use (“Terms of Service”) carefully before using Adportal, which will be referred to in this document as “this site.” By using this Site, you agree to these Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. Arkansas Online reserves the right to terminate or deny access to this Site to any person who violates these Terms of Service, or for any other reason.

1\. Introduction and Purpose of this Site.  
This Site is owned and operated by Arkansas Online on behalf of its participating print publications for the purpose of facilitating your purchase and placement of advertising content in those publications.

2\. Applicability and Acceptance of Terms of Use.  
By accessing or otherwise using this Site, you expressly agree to these Terms of Service as a binding legal agreement between you and Arkansas Online. Arkansas Online reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update these Terms of Service without prior notice. You will be notified of any such changes by an updated posting of the new Terms of Service on this page of the Site. Arkansas Online may modify, suspend, discontinue or restrict the use of any portion of the Site without notice or liability.

3\. Advertising Submitted by Users.  
a. Confirming your Order for an advertisement (“Advertising”) through this Site constitutes acceptance of these Terms of Service, Standards of Acceptability, and applicable provisions of the publications you selected to publish your Advertising.

b. All advertisements must include the name of the Advertiser. Physical address of advertiser must be on file.

c. All property rights, including any copyright interest in advertisements produced for an Advertiser by Arkansas Online, using art work and/or typography furnished or arranged by Arkansas Online, shall be the sole property of Arkansas Online. No such advertisement or any part thereof may be reproduced without the prior written consent of Arkansas Online.

d. Arkansas Online reserves the right to edit, revise or reject any advertising. Advertiser agrees to indemnify and save harmless Arkansas Online against any loss, damage, cost and expense (including, without limitation, attorney’s fees) which Arkansas Online may incur, or become liable for, by reason of any and all claims or actions for libel, violation of any right of privacy, plagiarism, copyright infringement, and any and all other claims of any kind or nature in connection with advertising matter published or advertiser by Arkansas Online.

e. Arkansas Online shall have no liability whatsoever in the event of any act of God, the public enemy or governmental authority, labor dispute, war (whether or not declared), civil disobedience, riot, failures of equipment or systems of Arkansas Online or its suppliers, or other occurrences beyond its control that shall in any way restrict or prevent the distribution of its newspapers and/or publication of the advertising.

f. No allowance will be made for advertisements appearing in other than requested positions.

g. Arkansas Online shall have no liability whatsoever, including without limitation any liability for consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages for not publishing any advertisement or by reason of any error in connection with any advertisement (including, without limitation, typographical errors, failure to publish advertising on desired dates, omissions or additions to advertisement\[s\]); provided, however, that Arkansas Online shall be obligated to adjust or rebate the charge on any advertisement or any portion of an advertisement which has been materially affected by an error of Arkansas Online; and provided further, however, that Arkansas Online’s obligation to give such credit shall not apply to more than one incorrect insertion of such advertisement unless and until Arkansas Online is notified of the error 24 hours prior to repetition of the insertion. Advertisers must notify Arkansas Online of any errors occurring when they appear, as per contract agreement. No adjustments will be made, honored or accepted more than 30 days after billing.

h. The agreements, conditions, rates and regulations set forth herein or in any written advertising contract between Arkansas Online and advertiser constitute the entire agreement between advertiser and Arkansas Online. In order to insure the accuracy of all space reservations, all verbal reservations must be confirmed in writing by the day of the actual space deadline, or within 24 hours. Arkansas Online is not responsible for any error in scheduling if no written confirmation is received.

i. The use of coupons in advertisements is encouraged, and care is taken to position the coupon ads to avoid printing coupons back-to-back. Due to press limitations and emergency make-up changes, however, it is possible that coupons may print back-to-back. No rebates or make-goods will be allowed in any event and for any reason.

j. Cancellations, changes of insertion dates and/or corrections must conform to published deadlines.  
k. Color ads scheduled subject to availability. If color is not available on selected date, ad may run in black and white and color charge rebated back to customer, or new schedule date may be selected.

4\. Payment.  
Payment is due in accordance with the payment provisions that apply to your Order. No order is considered accepted by Arkansas Online until approval is given for that order by Arkansas Online’s credit office. No advertisement shall be considered accepted by Arkansas Online until published. Any advertisement is subject upon submission to Arkansas Online’s applicable Contract & Copy Regulations, which may be changed at any time and from time-to-time in Arkansas Online’s sole discretion. Disclaimers on orders submitted by advertiser are ineffective and void unless expressly accepted by Arkansas Online.

5\. Cancelations.  
Ads may be cancelled with a full refund two (2) days prior to the first published date. Any advertisement cancelled after this time will be subject to the package rate that applies. No refund available on pre-paid packages. Press time limitations require two days to add or remove an advertisement from our Classified section of the newspaper

6\. Site Content.  
All information, content, services and software available on this Site (collectively, the “Content”) is protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws. The Content is owned by Arkansas Online, its Affiliates, and/or their respective licensors and suppliers (collectively, “Licensors”).

7\. Software.  
All software programming, including without limitation all HTML and other code contained in this Site (collectively, “Software”), is owned by Arkansas Online and/or its Licensors and is protected by copyright laws and other intellectual property laws, including international treaty provisions. Any unauthorized access to, reproduction, redistribution, publication, display or other use of the Software is expressly prohibited by law and may result in severe civil and/or criminal penalties.

8\. Privacy Policy.  
The following statement has been developed to demonstrate the commitment that Arkansas Online has to your privacy. Arkansas Online collects personal information to determine which products, features and special offers will benefit our users. Arkansas Online will send emails (to those who have elected to receive them) informing registered users of the offers and features that are of interest to them. Arkansas Online will not sell or give any personally identifiable information to our advertisers.

a. Arkansas Online collects personally identifiable information (name, e-mail address, etc.) and/or demographic data (zip code, etc.) that you submit when you register for our services, complete a survey, or send us an email.

b. Arkansas Online may use this information to process and maintain your account, compile demographic statistics about our users, and display to you information and advertisements that match your interests and profile.

c. Arkansas Online may use the contact information you provide to contact you about your account and/or to send you necessary information directly related to the product(s) or service(s) for which you have registered. With your permission, Arkansas Online may use your contact information to inform you of new features and special offers from us. Arkansas Online will not provide your contact information to unaffiliated third parties without your express permission. As part of the registration process, you have the option to inform us that you do not wish to receive information about other special offers and promotions.

d. IP Addresses and Cookies. Arkansas Online use IP addresses (random numbers assigned to individual computers) to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer our web site, and anonymously track content preferences and traffic patterns. Arkansas Online also use cookies (small text files transferred from our Web site to your hard drive) to recognize repeat users, track usage behavior, and facilitate your access to and use of our site. Cookies do not damage files or allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information; they simply allow us to tailor information and advertisements to make your visits more enjoyable and meaningful (and enable us to provide you with personalized information, if you choose). They also provide information to us about site usage to help us improve and update our site.

e. Security and Links. The security of the information you provide to us is important to Arkansas Online. We use encryption software and other security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of sensitive information under our control.

f. Children’s Online Privacy. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) stipulates that Web site operators cannot knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13 without verifiable parental permission. You must be 18 years or older to use this site.

g. Arkansas Online reserves the right to alter our Privacy Policy as business needs require. Any changes will be posted to our web site in a timely manner. This statement and the policies outlined here are not intended to and do not give you any contractual or other legal rights.

9\. Contact Us.  
To contact us, please use the following: Arkansas Online, Little Rock, AR 72201, jholmes@arkansasonline.com, (501) 918-4537

Deadlines for Classified Advertising
====================================

* For Monday or Tuesday - Fri 4PM
* For Wednesday - Mon 4PM
* For Thursday - Tue 4PM
* For Friday - Wed 4PM
* For Saturday - Thu 4PM
* Sunday Real Estate - Thu 3 PM
* All other Sunday - Fri. 3PM

Arkansas Online Free ad criteria
================================

* Available to Arkansas residents only
* Must run 3 days and be within 3 lines
* Must include price in ad and fall below $10,000;
* One free ad per category at a time;
* Maximum of 4 free ads per calendar month is allowed.
* This is per household not phone number
* Employment, Rental and Real Estate, Services, Garage Sales ,Firewood for sale ads and commercial items do not qualify for the free ad program.
* Commercial Packages are available

#### PLACE A CLASSIFIED AD

#### ACCOUNT

© 2024 Arkansas Democrat-Gazette, Inc  
All Rights Reserved.  
[Terms of Use](https://classifieds.arkansasonline.com/marketplace-littlerock/page/terms.html) / [Privacy Policy](https://classifieds.arkansasonline.com/marketplace-littlerock/page/privacy.html)

[iPublish® Marketplace powered by iPublish® Media Solutions © Copyright 2024](http://www.ipublishmedia.com/)
